Select Page

PRIVACY NOTICE
==============

**Effective Date: March 1, 2023**

Digital ReLab, LLC (“Digital ReLab”) cares about online privacy and wants you to know how we collect, use, share, and protect information about you and the choices you have regarding our use of your information. If you have any questions concerning this Privacy Notice, please email us at [privacy@starchive.io](mailto:privacy@starchive.io)**.**  This Privacy Notice applies to anyone who visits or uses any Digital ReLab website (singularly and collectively referred to herein as the “Website”), or uses, subscribes to, or licenses any Digital ReLab goods or services, including without limitation any of our software solutions, APIs, mobile applications, television applications, or other such service made available through Digital ReLab that may require the collection of your personal information (the “Services”).

**PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY NOTICE CAREFULLY TO UNDERSTAND OUR POLICIES AND PRACTICES REGARDING YOUR INFORMATION AND HOW WE WILL TREAT IT. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH OUR POLICIES AND PRACTICES, YOUR CHOICE IS NOT TO USE OUR WEBSITE AND/OR SERVICES.**  

We may change or add to this Privacy Notice from time to time, so we encourage you to review it periodically. The most recent version of the Privacy Notice will be posted on the Website, with the “Revised Date” posted at the top of the Policy. The Revised Date will change if we make any material changes to our Privacy Notice or how we handle your personal information.  If we make a significant or material change in the way we use your PII, we will post a more prominent notice (including, for certain Services, email notification of Privacy Notice changes where possible) in advance of any such change for thirty (30) days if feasible.  Your continued use of this Website or the Services after we make changes is deemed to be acknowledgement and acceptance of those changes.

**SCOPE.**  This Privacy Notice applies to the collection of personal information from users of the Website or Services, including any updated and new products or services that may be offered in the future by Digital ReLab.  It relates to information we collect from you, including personally identifying information (also referred to as “PII”) and information that does not identify you personally. PII may include, for example, some or all of the following: your name, mailing address, email address, telephone number, mobile phone number, user name, and password. By agreeing to any of our subscription agreements or Terms of Use, you acknowledge that you have read and understand our privacy practices. 

**INFORMATION COLLECTED AND USED BY DIGITAL RELAB.**  When users sign up for an account or submit information via the Website or the Services, Digital ReLab may collect user-submitted information such as name, profile photograph, social media account information, mailing address, telephone number, and email address. Digital ReLab uses that information to authenticate users and to send notifications to users relating to the Website, Services, or related materials or opportunities.

As is standard practice, Digital ReLab may also log non-personally identifying information, including IP address, profile information, aggregate user data, browser type, and device type from the Website and through the Services. This data is used to improve the services, analyze trends, administer the Website and Services, track users’ movements while using the Website or Services, and gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes.

In addition, Digital ReLab uses technological measures, such as pixel tags – tiny graphic images – to tell us what parts of the Website or Services have been visited or to measure the effectiveness of searches users perform. These technological measures also enable us to send email messages in a format that users can read, and they tell us whether emails have been opened to assure that we are only sending messages that are of interest to our users.

Digital ReLab may also use a user’s email address to send updates, newsletters, or news regarding the Services. Digital ReLab may send email messages which use a “click-through URL” linked to content on the Website and Services. When a user clicks one of these URLs, they pass through our web server before arriving at the destination web page. Digital ReLab may track this click-through data to help determine interest in particular topics and measure the effectiveness of our user communications. If you prefer not to be tracked you may simply avoid clicking the text or graphic links in the email. Users who no longer wish to receive promotional messages or updates may do so by opting-out. To opt-out, click the “unsubscribe” link in the email or reply with the word “unsubscribe” in the subject line of the email. 

We use the information that we collect to develop, deliver, and improve our Website, Services, and other offerings. In cases where you use a mobile device to access the Website and use the Services, we may receive information about the location of your device. 

**Rights in respect of your Information.** The laws of some countries grant particular rights in respect of personal information. Individuals in certain countries, including the European Union, United Kingdom, and Brazil have the right to:

* Request access to their information;
* Request that we correct inaccuracies in their information;
* Request that their information be deleted or that we restrict access to it;
* Request a structured electronic version of their information; and
* Object to our use of their information.

Should you wish to make a request in respect of your personal information please contact us at [privacy@starchive.io.](mailto:privacy@starchive.io) You also have the right to object to our processing of personal data about you in for marketing purposes and we will stop processing data for that purpose.

**USE OF COOKIES.** Digital ReLab uses cookies to store users’ preferences and to record session information for purposes including: (i) to customize our Website or Services content based on browser type and user profile information; (ii) to help track usage to help us understand which parts of the Website or Services are most popular, where our visitors are going, and how much time visitors spend in those parts; (iii) to make our Website and Services even more rewarding for users; (iv) to study the effectiveness of our user communications; and (v) to customize each user’s experience and provide greater convenience in navigating the Website or Services.  These cookies may reflect de-identified demographic or other data linked to data you voluntarily submitted to us, such as your email address. 

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since each browser is a little different, look at your browser’s Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, please note that some parts of the Website or Services may be inaccessible or not function properly, or your experience may be less efficient.

**LINKS AND EMBEDDED CONTENT.**  This Website and Services may contain links to third party sites or embedded content that is hosted through, or may redirect you to, a third-party site. Digital ReLab is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites or in embedded content. Our Privacy Notice only governs information collected on our Website and in connection with our Services; for information about third-party’s privacy practices, please visit that site’s privacy notice.

**CORRECTING/UPDATING OR REMOVING INFORMATION.**  Digital ReLab users and account owners may modify or remove any of the information contained in their account profile at any time by logging into their account and accessing features such as Member Settings. 

**SECURITY.**  Digital ReLab user accounts are secured by user-created passwords or other token-based authentication processes. Digital ReLab takes commercially reasonable precautions to ensure that account information is kept private, but keeping your information secure also depends on you. Sharing your account information with others is prohibited, and we also recommend that you avoid logging in to your account on an unsecured device.    

Digital ReLab uses reasonable measures such as encryption to protect private information stored within our database against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction, and we restrict access to such private information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions, such as our member service personnel and technical staff.  For example, when you enter sensitive information on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer (SSL) technology, which creates an encrypted connection between you and our systems. 

Please note that no method of electronic transmission or storage is 100% secure and Digital ReLab cannot guarantee the security of user account information.  Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of user information. In most cases, users will access their account via a secure authentication link or token.  Users are urged to also take precautions to protect their personal data by utilizing a strong password, consisting of a combination of letters, numbers, and special characters; and using a secure web browser, when using a password to access your account. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We cannot guarantee the security of your personal information and are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website or in the Services.

**THIRD PARTY LOG-IN.**  If you activate your account or log in to the Website or Services using a third-party for log-in purposes, your log-in information will be subject to the privacy practices of that third-party.    If you choose to utilize third-party log-in services, please review the third-party policies carefully and know that the use of this service at your own risk.     

**SHARING AND DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION DIGITAL RELAB COLLECTS.**  Except as otherwise described in this Privacy Notice, Digital ReLab will not disclose personal information to any third party unless it believes that disclosure is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant, or other legal process received by Digital ReLab, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce any of our license agreements or to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of the Services.  Digital ReLab may, in its sole discretion, but has no obligation to, review any and all information stored within its system.   

Digital ReLab reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of Digital ReLab or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest. Digital ReLab takes your privacy very seriously. To help us provide superior service, your personal information may be shared internally within Digital ReLab. We may also provide your personal information to companies that help us process information, deliver products to you, manage and enhance user data, provide user service, assess your interest in our products and Services, or conduct user research or satisfaction surveys. These companies are also obligated to protect your personal information in accordance with Digital ReLab’s policies.  Digital ReLab does not sell or rent your information to other parties.  

**AI and/or ML MODEL TRAINING.** Digital ReLab does not use any client data to train AI and/or ML models. We affirm that Google Workspace APIs are not used to develop, improve, or train generalized/non-personalized AI and/or ML models. Any transfer of data whether from Google or other 3rd party providers is not used for generalized/non-personalized AI/ML models.

**SHARING OF PAYMENT INFORMATION.**  Digital ReLab utilizes a secure third-party processor called Stripe (the “Payment Processor”) to process payments.  A link to the Payment Processor’s privacy practices is available at https://stripe.com/us/privacy.  Please refer to their privacy notice for more information about their privacy and security practices.  Digital ReLab does not receive or store your payment information.  Digital ReLab may receive information regarding your zip code and country as part of the payment transaction, which Digital ReLab may use to comply with tax and other government regulations.

**PRIVACY OF CHILDREN.**  We do not knowingly collect PII from those under the age of thirteen (13). If you believe that we have inadvertently collected PII from a person under thirteen (13), please contact us at [privacy@starchive.io](mailto:privacy@starchive.io) so that we can investigate and take any necessary remedial measures.

**CONTACTING US.**  If you have any questions about this Privacy Notice or our privacy practices, please contact us at: [privacy@starchive.io](mailto:privacy@starchive.io).  Inquiries can also be sent to the following physical mailing address:

Digital ReLab, LLC dba / Starchive  
Attn: Legal Department – Privacy

240 W Main St  
Suite #100-245  
Charlottesville, VA 22902

Less Organizing. More Control. Greater Freedom
----------------------------------------------

Store everything from video to images, audio to documents.

You can use our Free version to get the hang and feel 

When you are ready to [upgrade your plan](https://www.starchive.io/upgrade), we’ll be here to celebrate!

Starchive is a modern app to help you store every digital file you’ll ever create and collect and instantly organize it at your fingertips. Save it to the cloud and access it from your pocket anytime, anywhere.

Starchive is an inspired creative company and a team of people who respect people and privacy. Inspired and want to collaborate? [Join our team.](https://www.starchive.io/careers)

#### My Account

#### Pricing

#### Platform

#### Help & Support

#### Resources

#### Policies

#### Say Hello!

Looking to connect? DM us on social or [use this form](https://www.starchive.io/contact) to contact our co-founders directly.

Got 20 minutes? Pick a time to [schedule a call](https://api.leadconnectorhq.com/widget/bookings/starchive-intro-call) with us. We promise to be helpful and never boring.

Help shape the future of Starchive [share your feedback](https://www.starchive.io/community#social-uploader) with us.

Need Support? Please email support@starchive.io

Copyright © 2024 Digital ReLab LLC dba / Starchive • 240 W Main St, Suite #100-245 Charlottesville, VA 22902

We built part of this site while listening to sides 1 and 2 of “_Music from Big Pink_ by The Band”.

By clicking “Accept All”, you consent to our website's use of cookies to give you the most relevant experience by remembering your preferences and repeat visits. However, you may visit “Cookie Settings” to provide controlled consent.

Cookie settingsACCEPT

Manage consent

Close

#### Privacy Overview

This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.  
  
For more information please refer to our [privacy notice](https://www.starchive.io/privacy-notice/)

Necessary

 Necessary

Always Enabled

Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. These cookies ensure basic functionalities and security features of the website, anonymously.

| Cookie | Duration | Description |
| --- | --- | --- |
| \_\_hssrc | session | This cookie is set by Hubspot whenever it changes the session cookie. The \_\_hssrc cookie set to 1 indicates that the user has restarted the browser, and if the cookie does not exist, it is assumed to be a new session. |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-necessary | 1 year | Set by the GDPR Cookie Consent plugin, this cookie is used to record the user consent for the cookies in the "Necessary" category . |
| viewed\_cookie\_policy | 1 year | The cookie is set by the GDPR Cookie Consent plugin to store whether or not the user has consented to the use of cookies. It does not store any personal data. |

Functional

 functional

Functional cookies help to perform certain functionalities like sharing the content of the website on social media platforms, collect feedbacks, and other third-party features.

| Cookie | Duration | Description |
| --- | --- | --- |
| \_\_cf\_bm | 30 minutes | This cookie, set by Cloudflare, is used to support Cloudflare Bot Management. |
| \_\_hssc | 30 minutes | HubSpot sets this cookie to keep track of sessions and to determine if HubSpot should increment the session number and timestamps in the \_\_hstc cookie. |

Analytics

 analytics

Analytical cookies are used to understand how visitors interact with the website. These cookies help provide information on metrics the number of visitors, bounce rate, traffic source, etc.

| Cookie | Duration | Description |
| --- | --- | --- |
| \_\_hstc | 1 year 24 days | This is the main cookie set by Hubspot, for tracking visitors. It contains the domain, initial timestamp (first visit), last timestamp (last visit), current timestamp (this visit), and session number (increments for each subsequent session). |
| \_ga | 2 years | The \_ga cookie, installed by Google Analytics, calculates visitor, session and campaign data and also keeps track of site usage for the site's analytics report. The cookie stores information anonymously and assigns a randomly generated number to recognize unique visitors. |
| \_gat\_UA-62402144-3 | 1 minute | A variation of the \_gat cookie set by Google Analytics and Google Tag Manager to allow website owners to track visitor behaviour and measure site performance. The pattern element in the name contains the unique identity number of the account or website it relates to. |
| \_gid | 1 day | Installed by Google Analytics, \_gid cookie stores information on how visitors use a website, while also creating an analytics report of the website's performance. Some of the data that are collected include the number of visitors, their source, and the pages they visit anonymously. |
| ajs\_anonymous\_id | never | This cookie is set by Segment.io to check the number of ew and returning visitors to the website. |
| ajs\_user\_id | never | The cookie is set by Segment.io and is used to analyze how you use the website |
| CONSENT | 2 years | YouTube sets this cookie via embedded youtube-videos and registers anonymous statistical data. |
| hubspotutk | 1 year 24 days | This cookie is used by HubSpot to keep track of the visitors to the website. This cookie is passed to Hubspot on form submission and used when deduplicating contacts. |

Advertisement

 advertisement

Advertisement cookies are used to provide visitors with relevant ads and marketing campaigns. These cookies track visitors across websites and collect information to provide customized ads.

| Cookie | Duration | Description |
| --- | --- | --- |
| \_fbp | 3 months | This cookie is set by Facebook to display advertisements when either on Facebook or on a digital platform powered by Facebook advertising, after visiting the website. |
| fr  | 3 months | Facebook sets this cookie to show relevant advertisements to users by tracking user behaviour across the web, on sites that have Facebook pixel or Facebook social plugin. |
| test\_cookie | 15 minutes | The test\_cookie is set by doubleclick.net and is used to determine if the user's browser supports cookies. |
| VISITOR\_INFO1\_LIVE | 5 months 27 days | A cookie set by YouTube to measure bandwidth that determines whether the user gets the new or old player interface. |
| YSC | session | YSC cookie is set by Youtube and is used to track the views of embedded videos on Youtube pages. |
| yt-remote-connected-devices | never | YouTube sets this cookie to store the video preferences of the user using embedded YouTube video. |
| yt-remote-device-id | never | YouTube sets this cookie to store the video preferences of the user using embedded YouTube video. |

Others

 others

Other uncategorized cookies are those that are being analyzed and have not been classified into a category as yet.

| Cookie | Duration | Description |
| --- | --- | --- |
| \_hp2\_id.3582426800 | 1 year 1 month | No description |
| \_hp2\_ses\_props.3582426800 | 30 minutes | No description |
| ajs\_group\_id | never | This cookie is set by Segment.io. The purpose of the cookie is currently not identified. |
| debug | never | No description available. |

Save & Accept
